AI coding keeps getting better and
better. Cursor came first and it was
basically VS Code with AI features added
on top. Then we got AI in our terminals.
Now Claude Code is one of the best
coding agents out there. But what if I
told you that today I found something
truly amazing? Something that makes
Claude Code work all by itself. It
creates a whole team. And this team
doesn't work one thing at a time. They
all work together at the same time. The
best part, you don't need to monitor
anything because it's a truly autonomous
system that just works. Before I show
you the workflow, there are two key
concepts you need to understand since
many people won't be familiar with them.
By understanding these, you'll see why
this workflow is so amazing and how it
defines the way AI agents may work in
the future. The first is T-Mox, which
stands for terminal multiplexer. It's a
program that lets you create multiple
terminal sessions inside one window.
What this means is that when an agent
like Claude Code is running in a
terminal, it can spawn additional
terminals within the same session and
assign tasks to them. One instance of
Cloud Code can effectively control and
manage as many Claude Code instances as
it wants. The best part is that T-Max
sessions persist in memory, so when you
return to them, you're exactly where you
left off. This is incredibly useful for
maintaining context. The second concept
is terminal scheduling. This allows you
to assign tasks to agents with specific
timing parameters. You can instruct them
to perform certain actions at designated
times, then automatically proceed to the
next task. There's no need for constant
monitoring. The agents simply follow the
schedule you've created, completing
everything automatically. That's the
power of scheduling. It transforms your
terminal into a self-running system.
Over on the AI Labs Discord community,
we're hosting our first ever hackathon
from July 22nd to July 28th. Submit your
most interesting builds and projects,
and the top five submissions will be
featured in one of our YouTube videos.
You can join by clicking the link in the
pinned comment below. And if you're
enjoying the content so far, make sure
to hit that subscribe button so you
don't miss what's coming next. Before we
start, navigate to the directory or
folder where you want the system to be
set up. Once you're there, go to the
GitHub repository linked in the
description below. This repository is
called T-Max Orchestrator, and you'll
need to copy the link from there. Go
back to your terminal and type git clone
followed by the link. This command will
clone the repository to your local
machine. After cloning, move into the
new directory called T-Max Orchestrator.
And once inside, you'll run the setup
commands shown here. You don't need to
copy these commands from the video.
Later, I'll show you how to get them in
a structured format for easy copy and
paste. Running the setup executes
scripts that enable the agentic
workflow. This step makes all necessary
files executable. Once the setup is
complete, you need to start a new T-mok
session. Since I already have one
running, I'll name this one my second
agent. This will initialize a fresh
session for you. Before you start
working with the system, you need to fix
two things. Since this project is still
in development and relatively new, not
everything has been finalized. There are
two errors in the repository that need
correction. After fixing these, the
system should run properly. Both fixes
I'm about to explain require editing
files inside the framework. This will
make more sense when I show you the
demo. These are minor changes that you
can easily make yourself. First, when
you're inside the T-Mox session, type
out Claude to initialize Claude code.
You'll then give it a specific prompt
that explains how the orchestrator
works. There are two checks to ensure
everything is functioning correctly. The
first check verifies that Claude can
control different windows using T-Mox.
The second check confirms the scheduling
system is working. When I run this
prompt, it passes successfully. However,
when you run it, the check will fail
because the author has hard-coded paths
with their own username in the
configuration files. Don't worry about
this failure. Claude will automatically
detect the issue and fix these paths to
work with your system. You won't need to
copy this prompt from the screen either.
Moving on to the second fix. You need to
ask Claude code to edit the files again.
This time, tell it to look through all
the commands and replace the claude
command with the claude command using
the dangerously skip permissions flag.
This change is necessary because the
original framework we cloned doesn't
include this feature. As you can see,
there are three terminals that one main
agent is controlling. This is the key
benefit of using the T-Mox system. It
allows the main agent you just set up to
automatically create new terminals
within your main terminal window. This
is my main terminal and it has created
three sub terminals inside. While I'm
showing you three, there are actually
eight terminals running here. Normally,
when you give Claude a command, it asks
for your permission. Even with
autoaccept edits enabled, Claude still
requires approval for certain commands.
With the dangerous skip permissions
flag, Claude runs all commands
automatically. I've used this flag many
times without any system issues. You
need this setting so all the different
terminals can run Claude commands
without requiring you to open each one
and approve every action. I learned this
the hard way. My first time using the
system, I started it but noticed it was
stuck. Even after 15 minutes with the
scheduling system, everything remained
frozen at the first phase. This happened
because all the terminals were waiting
for my approval. You need to enable this
flag. So the system can execute all
commands independently without waiting
for your input. You've seen the multiple
terminal setup, but there's another
crucial part that requires your
attention. This is where you'll spend
most of your time, and it's what makes
the entire system worthwhile. I've
opened the project directory and cursor
to visually explain the structure. You
can see our T-Mox orchestrator folder
that we cloned. Outside of that, I have
an app folder containing two subfolders,
spec and task manager. The spec folder
contains the documentation that the
T-Max Orchestrator uses as its
blueprint. The task manager folder is
where the actual app gets built. The
spec folder is critical. It contains the
main spec, integration spec, and
separate front-end and backend specs.
These files provide guidelines that tell
the orchestrator exactly what app to
build. The main spec includes timing for
each development phase. Everything is
timed and Claude Code must complete each
phase within its allocated time frame.
I've prepared a template you can use to
create your specs step by step. It
includes default requirements for a full
stack web app, which you can modify
based on your needs. If you're building
something different, make sure to review
and adjust the specifications
accordingly. Once your spec is ready,
you'll use a specific prompt to start
cla working on the project. After this
point, everything runs autonomously.
Here's what you need to know about the
prompt. You must provide the full path
to your spec folder starting from the
home directory. Don't use relative
paths. Next, specify what teams to
create. There's a front-end team and a
back-end team, each with a project
manager and developer. You can add more
teams using the same format. For
example, to add authentication, you type
create an O team and follow the same
pattern. The system builds according to
your spec and checks on each team every
15 minutes to ensure tasks are completed
on schedule. It also commits changes
regularly, creating restore points in
case anything goes wrong. Version
control is built into the workflow. Let
me demonstrate my setup. I've reached my
Claude usage limit, so I can't show live
coding, but I can walk through how I
started the workflow. After completing
the two fixes and creating the T-Max
session, initialize Claude again using
the dangerous permissions flag. This
launches Claude with the necessary
permissions. Then provide your prompt
and the system will begin building
everything automatically. Let me show
you the terminals it opens and how it
manages the coding process across them.
This is the start of the project. I
initialized it exactly as I showed you.
To be safe, I ran the check command
mentioned at the beginning. Since I had
already fixed the hard-coded paths, it
confirmed the setup was successful. It
recognized the first agent window and
verified the scheduling was correct. I
provided the full stack app
specification and you can see it adding
what I wanted to build just as I
demonstrated earlier. After that, it
proceeded automatically. I also included
a UI implementation reference in the
front-end spec. It knows to check the UI
reference folder. Inside I have a design
image to replicate and a UI
implementation.m MD file. This
implementation plan provides exact steps
using Shad CN components with the Shad
CN MCP. It's an amazing workflow that
I'll link in the description if you're
interested. The system understood my
project requirements. It needed to
deploy the front-end team, then the
backend team, set up their development
phases, and schedule 15minute checkups.
It completed all these tasks. You can
see it briefing both teams using the
send claude message script. It sent
instructions to the front-end team's
project manager, then provided them with
the project specifications from the spec
folder. It repeated this process for the
backend team, giving them their schedule
and updating the to-do list. It marked
completed tasks and moved to the next
phase. The system informed me that both
teams were actively working. It provided
a status update and scheduled the next
check detailing what each team was doing
and their current progress. Both teams
were successfully deployed and working
on phase 1. After 15 minutes, the
orchestrated check-in report showed both
teams were ahead of schedule. Phase 1
was complete with bonus features added.
The 15-minute update confirmed phase 1
completion with several components
ready. It updated the to-do list and
asked permission to proceed with phase
2. You could configure the maind file to
proceed through all phases automatically
without asking. However, I prefer
step-by-step progression for review at
each checkpoint. Looking at the actual
setup, you can see our first agent at
the top. Below that is task front end
with three windows and task backend also
with three windows. Both teams work
simultaneously. Each has one window for
the project manager, another for the
developer, and a third for the server
that runs tests and checks for errors.
Everything operates in a closed loop.
These agents work and develop
independently. It's like having multiple
engineers working simultaneously, each
in their own terminal. This demonstrates
the true power that Demox brings to your
development workflow. At the bottom, you
can see the agent we created at the
start, which I named the second agent.
To understand the workflow and get all
the commands, you can head over to the
GitHub repository. However, it can be
confusing and I've made several
modifications myself. Instead, I
recommend using git ingest. Simply take
the GitHub URL and replace github.com
with gitingest.com. This will summarize
the entire repository into AI readable
text. Copy that summary and paste it
into Claude or chat GPT. From my
experience, Claude provides better
results for this type of task. Ask it to
explain the workflow and installation
process step by step, and it will guide
you through everything, including all
the necessary commands. If the commands
don't appear exactly as expected, don't
worry. I'll include all of them in the
description below for reference. That
brings us to the end of this video. If
you'd like to support the channel and
help us keep making videos like this,
you can do so by using the super thanks
button below. As always, thank you for
watching and I'll see you in the next
one.